SERGEY RADKOV

Boise ID 83713 | 208.283.90.8 | radkovsn@gmail.com

http://sergeyradkov.github.io www.linkedin.com/in/radkovsn https://github.com/sergeyradkov

Permanent Work Authorization No Visa Sponsorship Required Open to Relocation

TECHNOLOGIES

Proficiencies

HTML Node.js CSS NPM Bootstrap Bower

JavaScript Git / GitHub Angular.js Heroku

jQuery Visual Studio Code

Have experience with

Foundation MVC Pattern

Express Java
Twilio C#
Firebase .NET

JSData MS Studio Code MySQL IntelliJ IDEA

PROJECTS

https://qbemailgrabber.herokuapp.com

The web application is aimed to reduce time for administration of QuickBooks accounts by owners and engage their clients to provide addition information online without registration, built with Bootstrap, Angular, Node, Express, Twilio and Intuit API.

http://sergeyradkov.github.io/music-finder

The simple web page helps to find favorite music in the iTunes Store and plays samples, built with jQuery, Bootstrap and iTunes API.

http://sergeyradkov.github.io/inspire

The landing web page provides current time, weather conditions in Boise, the list of tasks, built with AngularJS, APIs.

http://sergeyradkov.github.io/pop-up-penguins/

The online game where it is necessary to find all penguins and don't meet a yeti, built with CSS and JavaScript.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Junior Web Developer with a passion for online businesses has extensive knowledge of business analysis and substantial experience creating logical and innovative solutions to complex problems to increase efficiency, with 5+ years' telematics service promotion and 8 years' management experience.

EDUCATION

Web Development Immersive Full Stack Course

BoiseCodeWorks \mid Boise, Idaho \mid 04/2016 – 06/2016 The leading premier coding bootcamp in Idaho.

Master's Degree | Transport Management

(combined bachelor/master program)

State University of Management | Moscow, Russia | 1997 – 2002 Russia's leading university in the field of management education

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Freelance | Boise, Idaho | 2016 - now

Created and maintained web pages using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, AngularJS and Node.js, optimized web pages for mobile, and debugged for better code, updated existing code and learned new technologies on the fly

Senior Product Engineer

Volvo Truck Russia | Moscow, Russia | 2010 -2015 A branch of Volvo Trucks, a global truck manufacturer.

Promoted Volvo telematics services, provided technical support for 600+ customers and 100+ team members, established new consulting service using Volvo's telematics.

Transportation Coordinator

TOTAL E&P Russia | Moscow, Russia | 2008 - 2010 Subsidiary of TOTAL S.A., a multinational oil and gas company.

Transportation Manager

Unimilk | Moscow, Russia | 2006 - 2007

Russia's largest dairy producer; now owned by Danone.

Transportation Specialist

PKD Optima | Moscow, Russia | 2003-2006 General distributor of Philip Morris USA in Russia

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Practical problem solver with exceptional attention to detail
- Strong presentation, communication and negotiation skills
- Demonstrated success in project and staff management
- Ability to adapt to rapidly changing environments
- International experience and bi-lingual in English and Russian